[
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 1,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 1",
    "respuesta": "60 km/h",
    "tiempo": 12
  },
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 2,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 2",
    "respuesta": "Triángulos de emergencia",
    "tiempo": 12
  },
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 3,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 3",
    "respuesta": "10 metros",
    "tiempo": 12
  },
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 4,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 4",
    "respuesta": "Obligación",
    "tiempo": 12
  },
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 5,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 5",
    "respuesta": "Cambiar de carril",
    "tiempo": 12
  },
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 6,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 6",
    "respuesta": "Detenerse y ceder el paso a otros vehículos",
    "tiempo": 12
  },
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 7,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 7",
    "respuesta": "0.05%",
    "tiempo": 12
  },
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 8,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 8",
    "respuesta": "Adelantar está prohibido",
    "tiempo": 12
  },
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 9,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 9",
    "respuesta": "120 km/h",
    "tiempo": 12
  },
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 10,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 10",
    "respuesta": "3 metros",
    "tiempo": 12
  }
]